so last weekend yeah we went swimming together and that was fun but like
i just don't know what it meant you know yeah i'm sorry i'm late
do you want to go there together yeah next sunday sound good to you
the season of happy kids awesome i'm back it's so hot outside
um why don't you have the air conditioner on
i think it broke
you've never been anything more than a
Oh, my God.
Okay, I'm back yet again.
Did you get us a new AC?
Yeah, but they won't be able to install it for three more days.
Oh, no. Three whole days?
Is there anything more worthless than humans?
Fascinating.
All right, then, for the time being at least,
let us go forth and make merry with our usual purgatorial feast.
C-c-c. I am still racist V. Felicity Sumeragi, right?
Even if I were to be surrounded with flames measuring 20 million degrees,
I would remain the great and mighty king of all the night.
Why don't you change into shorts or something?
This dress embodies my powers of darkness, stupid head.
I can't just take it off because I'm hot.
Yeah, right. You want some tea?
Is this episode new?
Oh, it's the one you recorded yesterday.
Here you go.
You backed me into a corner.
Who would believe it?
Now, gaze upon my true form.
Releasing binding spell.
Unleashing magic power.
Yes, this is my true form.
True form?
But it's so beautiful.
I guess the finale must be next week.
Brother, I'm releasing the binding spell.
I mean, releasing binding spell.
Why aren't you watching me?
Put everything you just took off into the washer.
Okay.
Unleashing magic power.
Now you may gaze upon my true form.
Rip off?
It's not a rip off.
I did not desire for it to be necessary to unleash my true power onto you.
Blame it on a particularly annoying season of hell.
I do only what I must.
Sure thing.
Whatever you say.
Hey, so listen.
I'm about to head out to the club.
You want to go with?
I mean, if you're allowed to go out wearing that.
They do have a working air conditioner.
Oh, go.
Hey, Kobito?
Yeah?
Those are clothes you wore in elementary school, aren't they?
I can't believe you still fit into them, even though you're in your second year of middle school.
I wonder if you've stopped growing already.
So what do I do about it?
I don't want to be this little forever.
Wait, now that I'm thinking about it, as a member of the night tribe, I'm supposed to be eternal.
Which means, of course, my body will never get discrepant or ugly with age.
That's a good point.
I'm glad you're not going to get discrepant.
You know, or decrepit.
It's whatever.
Hey, we're here.
You're late.
We're glad you made it nonetheless, Big Brother.
Hey, Big Brother!
Long time no see, huh?
Long like forever, right?
Yukimura got me sushi for lunch today.
How great is that?
And yesterday he gave me steak.
He's the best, isn't he, Big Brother?
Uh, sushi?
Steak?
Since you ordered me to make sure I only gave Miss Maria food that tasted good,
whatever I made for her, I prepared with every bit of my heart and soul.
Yeah, I know I said that, but I mean, aren't you going a bit overboard?
When you force-fed me that nasty medicine, I swore I was going to chop something important off of that she-mail.
But now that you're not crazy, it's different.
Thanks so much, Yukimura.
You should thank Big Brother, not me.
Thank you, Big Brother!
I love you so much!
You stupid!
Who do you think you are?
I hope you turn into a pig from everything you eat,
so then my brother will hate you and your nasty, fat guts!
Hey!
What was that?
Who the hell are you?
I'm my Big Brother's little sister, thank you!
Cute!
Hey, Kopitou!
You're that dummy vampire?
The one that tricked me?
Incarnation of darkness!
Be gone!
Ah!
She bit me!
Why would you do that?
Dummy, stupid-headed, dummy-head!
Of course she bit you.
That's what vampires do.
That's what you get, tool of God.
And now that you've been bitten by a real vampire,
your cursed fate shall be to become a vampire as well.
Is that true, Big Brother?
That is normally how these things work, yeah?
No!
I'm gonna turn into a vampire!
I don't want to turn into a vampire!
Maria, I've heard of you bathing the sun's rays
immediately after getting bitten.
It kills the curse and you won't turn into a vampire.
What?
Are you serious?
Of course I am.
Although it won't work if you wear clothes.
You have to be completely and utterly naked.
Okay, got it!
Thank you, Yosara!
You are really evil.
She's just so stupid, I can't help myself.
What do you want?
And please stop staring at me, it's weird.
Hopato, you are just the cutest thing!
But what happened to your goth lolly look?
I liked it.
I just unleashed my true power, no big deal.
I have no idea what that means,
but I cannot stand how adorable you are.
I want to eat you alive whenever I see you!
Please, don't do that.
Tell Rika something.
What kind of panties are you wearing?
You guys need to cut it out.
Just take them off so we can see them.
As God is my witness, I'm going to conquer that cutie Cobra Toe, too.
Behave yourself, perverts.
You're freaking around.
Shine on me!
The sun's rays!
God's light will save me!
The sucky thing about summer is there's nothing to do.
Yeah.
At this point, I would be okay with ten times the amount of summer homework they forced on us.
Well, speak for yourself.
While we're sitting here being bored to death,
I wonder what other people have decided to do with their free time.
They're having fun with their friends, obviously.
I wish all the happy people would just die.
I wish they'd die, too.
What did video game characters ever do to you?
Ha!
In this scene, if I were the writer of this game, I'd so put in a killer shark.
A shark?
What are you being all nasty for?
Come on, meat.
If a shark appeared out of nowhere and tore apart all those lame bimbos,
that would be an awesome god game, and you know it.
Except that doesn't make sense here, so it would never happen.
They're at a public pool, not in the freaking ocean.
Ah!
A shark!
There's no way that's a real shark, you guys.
Like, yeah, it's got to be a radio-controlled one or something normal like that.
Watch.
No way this game pulls something that cliché.
What is a real shark doing in a public pool?
This is so lame!
Breathe.
Now, it's a comedy, so we should wait for the punchline of the joke.
I can totally see how a shark in a public pool would set up a good laugh.
I predict the lead character ends up killing the shark in some hilarious way.
I bet that'll make my score go up.
No!
Mizuki!
You're right.
That was hilarious.
I've had enough of this shitty game!
The name of that game is called St. Jaws Academy Tale, right?
Yeah, one of it!
Rika heard the ending of it was supposed to be really bad.
Troll bad.
If you don't set up flags on St. Jaws, it not only throws you into a crappy ending,
but then it finishes with a nasty gore scene that practically comes out of nowhere.
It's, like, so random.
Actually, the game is kind of famous for being stupid.
I had no idea chick games could be so deep.
It's funny because I'd kill to go to a pool right now.
What?
You're saying this immediately after seeing a bunch of over-sexed heroines devoured by a shark at a public pool?
Does this mean you have a death wish?
Please say yes.
Are you trying to make sense?
Going swimming has nothing to do with that game.
I'd just really like to go to a pool, okay?
Oh, good.
I was getting worried.
Just know if you ever decide your fate is to be ripped to shreds by a shark,
I'll think about saving you for at least a second.
So you're welcome.
Uh, okay, thank you.
Me too.
I want to go to a pool.
Gravato, you can go with me if you want.
We'll have the most amazing time together.
Creepy meat returns.
A pool, huh?
Isn't that where happy people go?
If I'd made some friends yet, I bet I'd want to go to a pool, too.
It shouldn't be that hard of a decision for you.
I've been to Sea God's Palace Land before with Co-
Uh, hey, why don't we all go there together?
You know, as a club activity or something.
Call it a rehearsal for the real thing.
That doesn't suck too hard.
I mean, it's not like we have anything better to do.
Let's go.
Hey, Kodaka, try not to get too excited when you see Rika in her swimsuit.
I bet you wear a dress thing.
You know, like those cover-ups that keep people from seeing you in a suit?
What?
No, I don't.
To prove it, Rika will purchase a sexy new suit,
which is bound to make you drool all over her.
Low-cut leg, string bikini, a barely-bare number,
a Band-Aid piece, or nude for the whip!
I have no idea what half of those are.
Gross!
Guess she's excited.
Hey, sexy!
We're all over here!
You guys are always early.
No, we're not.
You're just late.
What's the deal?
We weren't supposed to meet here.
Ugh.
Holy crap!
It was like this when we got here.
I bet they're all headed to the pool, too.
I can't believe how awful this crowd is.
Hey, Yozara, are you feeling okay?
You look kind of sick.
I am.
It's not from the bus.
It's from all the people.
I feel real bad.
Uh, here.
I'm good.
I'm not gonna throw up.
Definitely not gonna throw up.
Definitely.
Rika's not gonna hurl either.
You feel sick, too?
Yep.
Rika's no good in crowds.
They make her real anxious.
But don't worry.
Rika's fine.
If she must,
she can easily find energy from you.
As in from below the belt.
Wow, that's great.
By the way,
when Yozara says definitely not gonna throw up,
is it kind of a turn-on,
or is that just Rika?
No, it's absolutely just Rika.
Are you only sick mentally?
So, Kobito,
what you wanna do when we get to the pool?
Go swim.
I guess that's obvious.
Would you like for me to teach you how to swim?
No.
I know how.
Of course you do.
What are you good at?
Long distance.
Cool.
Why don't we do that together?
No.
She's even adorable when she's being rude.
I know she's sweet on the inside, though.
Oh, no!
Are you okay?
Bro, a little help here, please.
Did you hurt yourself?
I don't like this at all.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I wonder if the sisters are a lot like...
We finally made it.
Yeah.
Hooray.
You see?
I told you I was fine.
I so did not throw up.
Yeah, way to go.
Yozara definitely did not hurl.
Wow, there are so many people here.
It wasn't like this last time at all.
I guess it's so hot, even commoners will cough up some money to go to the pool.
Curse this damn infertile sun.
Luckily, I exist in my true form now, so its race can no longer destroy me.
C-c-c-can we go in?
I'm so hot.
Look at that.
No wonder it's so freaking crowded.
We're risking our lives being here.
Why did we not do this in July?
Look on the bright side.
At least it's cheaper.
Who cares?
I'd rather pay twice as much than be forced to deal with these people.
I think their half-price sale could totally suck it.
Well, speak for yourself again.
Come on, let's go.
That took forever.
Here.
Thanks.
Shall we change and meet in front of the showers?
Yeah.
A girl.
Look at that.
I guess I'm just one of those girls who's instantly hated by all guys, even though I'm really a boy.
No, you're wrong.
That's not true.
Hey, he might not look like it, but this dude is totally a...
A guy!
Wait, I, um...
Yeah, you tell him, bro.
This should be fine.
I guess we should get changed.
Yes, that sounds good.
Why the hell did you bring a girl's swimsuit with you?
Because Yozora told me to.
She said that I should wear one today.
And why would you ever ask Yozora for advice?
Because Yozora has become my trusted advisor.
She had a good point.
I want my inner masculinity to shine through even when wearing women's clothing.
I thought this would be a good challenge for me.
Way too intense.
Well, I did bring along a man's swimsuit, too, just in case.
Dude, what's that?
Oh, it's a loincloth.
By all means, challenge yourself with the women's swimsuit.
I'll let you borrow the loincloth if you want to.
I don't.
Thanks, though.
Are you doing okay?
Do you need me to help you get into your suit?
No.
All right.
You need some help?
Yes, I'd appreciate it.
Calm down, Kotika.
He's a dude.
All set.
That was very nice.
Thank you.
Yeah.
How do girls put stuff like that on and take it off all by themselves?
Hey!
Is anything wrong?
Are you okay?
Why are you hiding your chest?
Because it's not very muscular and I'm embarrassed by it.
But if you really want to see it, I'll let you.
I don't want to see.
Just put your top back on already.
Understood, sir.
Uh.
It's about time.
What took you guys so long?
Nothing.
More importantly, I'd rather not talk about it.
Why is Yukimura wearing a girl's swimsuit?
I said I'd rather not talk about it.
Hey, wait.
Where are Yozara and Rika?
They told me they'd be out after they rested a bit.
Yeah.
It looked like that ride was pretty rough on both of them.
I'm gonna go swim now.
Yay, you guys!
It's so cold!
Hurry up, bro!
Coming.
Ooh.
Crazy.
Having this many people cannot be legal.
Long distances out.
Yeah, I can imagine that would be difficult.
Hmm.
This is gross and annoying.
I wish that shark would show up.
But I thought sharks were too cliche for you.
When the girls finally get out,
how about we head down to the Lazy River
and maybe the water slide?
Fine.
This is awful.
That it is.
It wasn't this bad last time we came.
No.
It was way better.
Yeah, way better until you got all mad at me.
Hmm?
What are you talking about?
You got mad at me!
No.
You were pissed.
But then when we were leaving,
what did you say thank you for?
What's going on?
Those girls are taking for freaking ever.
Guess so.
Hmm.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go check on them.
I wonder what she's upset about now.
I get it.
At the time, there were only three of us
in the neighbor's club.
We've got more members now.
Show me.
I guess we haven't exactly
made any friends yet either.
But depending on how you look at it,
I think we've all at least changed a lot.
Kodaka!
Yozara just sent me this message.
They went home?
Kodaka!
Where'd he go?
Yozara!
Rika!
You guys!
Don't go!
Come on!
Wait!
She's so stupid.
Why'd they have to leave?
I had planned to show off my ultra-elegant swimming form to her.
Or maybe we haven't changed after all.
What'd you say?
What?
Nothing.
Should we go home too?
Yeah.
The Neighbors Club Activity Report.
Today's activity, nothing.
Here's some shabu-shabu.
Meat! Meat! Meat!
Also some sushi.
Ramy! Ramy!
I made your steak, too.
It's marbled and delicious!
Boiled eel over rice.
I can't even see the rice! There's so much meat!
This is too yummy! I can't stop eating!
Thank you!
Oh!
I can't move anymore!
Oh, no!
I just had the worstest, most scariest dream
I've ever had in my whole life!
Next, the president's recollections are painful.
I'm never gonna eat again!
Your argent has grains.
All right, so...
What are your ład greetings?
Were you?
Oh, no?
What's that mean?
We have filho...
Together we have three fís' lobster